<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Niko Okio</title>
    <link>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Niko Okio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nikookio.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Growth Hacking Simpler than ever: Easy to follow Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/growth-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/growth-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Growth hacking is a term that is often used in the world of business and marketing. It refers to a set of strategies and techniques that are designed to help businesses grow quickly and efficiently.
At its core, growth hacking is about finding creative and unconventional ways to drive growth for a business. This can include a variety of tactics, such as using social media and other online platforms to reach new audiences, experimenting with different pricing models, and leveraging data and analytics to make informed decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most groundbreaking SaaS companies of 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/top-10-saas-business-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/top-10-saas-business-2022/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s start with an overview of the top SaaS startups we are going to cover! Zendesk is a customer service platform that allows businesses to manage their customer interactions more effectively. The company was founded in 2007 and has since grown to become one of the leading saas providers in the world. Salesforce is a CRM software provider that helps businesses track and manage their customer interactions. The company was founded in 1999 and has since grown to become one of the largest saas providers in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a SaaS application</title>
      <link>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/how-to-build-a-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/how-to-build-a-saas/</guid>
      <description>How to build a SaaS application A software as a service (SaaS) application is a software application delivered over the internet. SaaS applications are usually subscription based, with users paying a monthly or annual fee. If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking of building a SaaS application, there are a few things you&amp;rsquo;ll need to keep in mind. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through the high level process of building a SaaS application, from start to finish and how I&amp;rsquo;m tackling it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Digital Ocean is a great hosting platform for your SaaS product</title>
      <link>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/digital-ocean-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/digital-ocean-hosting/</guid>
      <description>What is Digital Ocean? Digital Ocean is a cloud computing platform that offers virtual private servers, or &amp;ldquo;droplets,&amp;rdquo; as they&amp;rsquo;re called. Droplets are typically used to host web applications, and they offer several benefits over traditional shared hosting environments.
For one, droplets are much more configurable than traditional shared hosting environments. This means that you can tailor your droplet to the specific needs of your application. For example, if you&amp;rsquo;re running a database-driven web application, you can choose to allocate more RAM and CPU resources to your droplet than if you were just running a simple static website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my journey</title>
      <link>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hi there 👋🏻
I&amp;rsquo;m Niko and starting to build in public! This can be a scary step in the beginning, because everything you do will be judged by the public. But on the other hand you get a lot of valuable inputs and feedback along the journey. So it&amp;rsquo;s defenitly worth it!
My Goal 🎯 for now is to launch 2+ Products in 2022, gain some customers that pay me and learn a lot of things on the go!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
