<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SaaS on Niko Okio</title>
    <link>https://www.nikookio.com/categories/saas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SaaS on Niko Okio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nikookio.com/categories/saas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to build a SaaS application</title>
      <link>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/how-to-build-a-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/how-to-build-a-saas/</guid>
      <description>How to build a SaaS application A software as a service (SaaS) application is a software application delivered over the internet. SaaS applications are usually subscription based, with users paying a monthly or annual fee. If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking of building a SaaS application, there are a few things you&amp;rsquo;ll need to keep in mind. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through the high level process of building a SaaS application, from start to finish and how I&amp;rsquo;m tackling it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Digital Ocean is a great hosting platform for your SaaS product</title>
      <link>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/digital-ocean-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nikookio.com/posts/digital-ocean-hosting/</guid>
      <description>What is Digital Ocean? Digital Ocean is a cloud computing platform that offers virtual private servers, or &amp;ldquo;droplets,&amp;rdquo; as they&amp;rsquo;re called. Droplets are typically used to host web applications, and they offer several benefits over traditional shared hosting environments.
For one, droplets are much more configurable than traditional shared hosting environments. This means that you can tailor your droplet to the specific needs of your application. For example, if you&amp;rsquo;re running a database-driven web application, you can choose to allocate more RAM and CPU resources to your droplet than if you were just running a simple static website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
